Joe Hollenbach

Software Engineer

linkedin.com/in/joe-hollenbach

github.com/justjoe19

joe-h.netlify.app

Summary

- Experience with Python, Django, HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React
- Experience with Mac and PC hardware repair and troubleshooting and repair
- · Experience with networking
- Job history of management and leadership experience

Skills

HTML; CSS; Javascript; Python; Java; Web Development; SQL; Node.js; Django; MongoDB; MySQL; Version Control; GitHub; Bash; Unix; Linux; Networking; Responsive Web Design; Cloud Computing; Hardware and Software Troubleshooting; Virtualization; Computer Repair; Technical Support; User Interface Design;

Education

Jan 2022 - Mar 2024

Front-End Development;

Object-Oriented Programming

South Bend, IN

Associate of Applied Science - Software Development

Ivy Tech Community College 3.8 GPA

Oct 2020 - Dec 2022 South Bend, IN

Technical Certificate in Software Development

Ivy Tech Community College 3.8 GPA

Work Experience

December 2021 - present

Mishawaka, IN

Apple, Inc. - Expert

- Perform face-to-face technical support for iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, and Mac
- Provide customers with issue troubleshooting, product diagnosis and potential solutions
- Leader in product sales, product knowledge, and customer satisfaction

January 2019 - June 2021

Mishawaka, IN

Jordan Auto Group - Acquisitions Manager

- In charge of purchasing and pricing up to 250vehicle inventory
- Merchandise and advertise each vehicle online using web application tools
- Oversee and support appraisal and reconditioning processes for each vehicle

Certifications

· A+ Certification

CompTIA, March 2024

- Software Application Developer Certificate
 Ivy Tech Community College, May 2023
- AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner
 Amazon Web Services, May 2023
- PC Pro Certification

TestOut Corporation, June 2021